Guide to the David Wojnarowicz Papers ca. 1954-1992 MSS 092
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- OVERSIZE - Series XI: Art Works
  - Subseries D: Source/Background Material
    - New York Post cover, Aug 10 1988 - "Some Cops Hid Badges. ." (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Print material - "Militant Eroticism Art" calendar, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - "Loteria Nacional" tables, undated (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - 2 Supermarket posters, undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - "The Sermon on the Mount", undated (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Patterned paper (handmade?), undated (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Comic strip - "Buck missing on Mercury!", undated (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Pumpkin cutout, undated (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Commercial logos - "I (heart) America;" "British Airways/London Bridge", undated (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Spanish-language posters (3), poster: "The Un-Work Force", undated (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Subseries E: Plans
    - Various plans, undated (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Lists & ideas for works, undated (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Subseries F: Xerox Art
    - Xerox art, undated (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Xerox art, undated (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Subseries G: Other People's Art
    - Various art by others, incl. Kiki Smith, undated (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Barbara Kruger, "Aqui!", undated (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Misc. Other People's Art, undated (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - "Oswald baby kidnapped" poster, undated (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Photo of Michael Roman Poster, "The Jimmies" (NYC summer 1984) (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Text - "The End of the USA", undated (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - "Don't Labor Under a Misconception!" - flyer, undated (Box 24, Folder 18)
- OVERSIZE - Series XII: Library
  Wojnarowicz Library List (note: Photography books may have originally belonged to Peter Hujar.)
  Most titles have been cataloged and can be retrieved by searching Bobcat, the Bobst library's online catalog.
  - Animals from Life. Chicago: Rand, McNally and Co.: 1900. [39] (Box 36, Folder 40)
  - Bacou, Roseline. Piranesi. Berlin: Rembrandt Verlag, 1975. (Box 36, Folder 82)
  - Bomb. No. 8, 1983/84. / Winter 1987. (Box 36, Folder 119)
  - Cordry, Donald. Mexican Masks. Austin: University of Texas Press, 1980. (Box 36, Folder 193)
  - Cover: Arts New York. Janury 1988. (Box 36, Folder 194)
  - Daily News. 11 Dec. 1989 (Box 37, Folder 201)
  - Grosz, George. Ecce Homo. Secaucus, NJ: Castle Books, 1965. (Box 37, Folder 296)
  - Hensley, Tim. Steam, Steel, and Stars. New York: Harry N. Abrams, 1987. (Box 37, Folder 327)
  - Holldobler, Bert and Edward O. Wilson. The Ants. Cambridge, MA: Harvard UP, 1990. (Box 38, Folder 335)
  - La Argentina. Buenos Aires: Guillermo Kraft Limitada, 1864., 1964 (Box 38, Folder 393)
  - Les Animaux D'Apres Nature. Paris: E. Bernard, 1905. (Box 39, Folder 404)
  - New York Native. Issue 329. 7 Aug. 1989 (Box 39, Folder 517)
  - New York Newsday. 11 Dec. 1989 (Box 39, Folder 518)
  - ---. 17 Jan. 1991 (Box 39, Folder 519)
  - ---. 21 Jan. 1991 (Box 39, Folder 520)
  - ---. 22 Jan. 1991 (Box 39, Folder 521)
  - ---. 24 Jan. 1991 (Box 40, Folder 522)
  - ---. 25 Jan. 1991 (Box 40, Folder 523)
  - ---. 29 Jan. 1991 (Box 40, Folder 524)
  - ---. 18 March 1991. (Box 40, Folder 525)
  - New York Post. 11 Dec. 1989 (Box 40, Folder 526)
  - ---. 14 June 1990. (Box 40, Folder 527)
  - ---. 18 June 1990. (Box 40, Folder 528)
  - ---. 17 Jan. 1991 (Box 40, Folder 529)
  - ---. 22 Feb. 1991 (Box 40, Folder 530)
  - ---. 7 March 1991. (Box 40, Folder 531)
  - ---. 14 Jan. 1991 (Box 41, Folder 532)
  - ---. 29 Jan. 1991 (Box 41, Folder 533)
  - ---. 20 April 1992. (Box 41, Folder 534)
  - O'Nirem, Dan. El mundo desconocido del amazonas. Caparra Terrace, Puerto Rico: Express Prints, 1983. (Box 41, Folder 539)
  - The Outlook. 25 July 1990. (Box 41, Folder 545)
  - Paper. March 1989. (Box 41, Folder 553)
  - Pieter Bruegel. New York: Harry N. Abrams Inc, 1969. [with inserts] (Box 41, Folder 573)
  - Pronto: US Retail & Trend Monitor. Vol. 2, No. 5 May 1985. (Box 41, Folder 588)
  - Rand McNally Road Atlas. Boston: Rand McNally & Co., 1991. (Box 42, Folder 595)
  - Singh, Raghubir. Calcutta. London: Thames and Hudson, 1988. (Box 42, Folder 643)
  - Stechow, Wolfgang. Pieter Bruegel the Elder. New York: Harry N. Abrams, [n. d]. [source material see pages 13 and 15. ], undated (Box 42, Folder 657)
  - Steiglitz, Alfred. Georgia O'Keefe. New York: Metropolitan Museum of Modern Art, 1978. (Box 42, Folder 658)
  - Ward, Lynd. Storyteller without Words. New York: Harry N. Abrams, 1974. (Box 43, Folder 715)
  - West Sussex Gazette. 13 May 1993. (Box 43, Folder 721)
  - Wingrove, David. The Immortals of Science Fiction. New York: Mayflower Books, 1980. (Box 43, Folder 731)
  - Ambrosius, Ernst and Konrad Frenzel. Das Bild der Erde. Bielefeld: Velhagen & Klafing, 1930. (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - Arader III, W. Graham. Native Grace. Charlottesville, VI: Thomasson-Grant, 1988. (Box 44, Folder 46)
  - Express. [K 2 Aug. 1986 (Box 44, Folder 249)
  - ---. [K 2 Sept. 1986 (Box 44, Folder 250)
  - The Voice. 26 June 1990. (Box 44, Folder 710)
  - National Geographic Atlas of the World. Washington D. C.: National Geographic Society, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 498)
  - Standard Atlas of Ford Country. Chicago: Geo. A. Ogle and Co., 1916. (Box 45, Folder 653)
  - State Farm Road Atlas. Bloomington, IL: The State Farm Insurance Co., 1939. (Box 45, Folder 656)
  - East Village Eye. Vol. V, No. 36, September 1983. /Vol. V, No. 53, May 1984. /Vol. VIII, No. 61, Dec/Jan 1986. /Vol. VIII, No. 63, March 1986. (Box 46, Folder 744)
  - Distributed Art Publishers, Catalogs, Spring 1992/Fall 1992. (Box 46, Folder 745)
  - Your House is Mine, An Act of Resistance 1988-1992. New York: Bullet Space, 1993, 1988-1993 (Box 46, Folder 746)
- Mapcase - Series VII: Subjects
  - Subseries C: Announcements
    - Argentina Posters, undated (Map-case 1.J, Folder 1)
    - "Cop Shoot Cop," Tues Apr 4, Pyramid; "Rock Barricada," Danceteria, April 1, undated (Map-case 1.J, Folder 2)
    - "Harry Kondoleon / Poet's Corner" Poster, undated (Map-case 1.J, Folder 3)
    - "Holidays in the Sun" (The Sex Pistols) Poster, undated (Map-case 1.J, Folder 4)
    - "Larry Clark and Peter Hujar, Frankfurter Kunstverein" Posters, undated (Map-case 1.J, Folder 5)
    - "Retrospective Posters", undated (Map-case 1.J, Folder 6)
    - "Silence = Death" / "Positive" Film Screening Poster, undated (Map-case 1.J, Folder 7)
    - Spanish-language Posters & Rose-Patterned Wrapping Paper, undated (Map-case 1.J, Folder 8)
    - "Ueber Sofa Auf die Strasse!" Poster, undated (Map-case 1.J, Folder 9)
    - Various Cultural & Political Posters, undated (Map-case 1.J, Folder 10)
- Mapcase - Series XI: Art Works
  - Subseries A: Finished/Original
    - "Democracy", undated (Map-case 1.J, Folder 11)
    - "Hunger", undated (Map-case 1.J, Folder 12)
    - Offset Plates - "Between C & D", "A Few Months Ago...", undated (Map-case 1.J, Folder 13)
    - Poster for "Electric Messages Beneath the Sea," Brigitte Engler, The Parallel Window; metal template for "Between C&D" poster, undated (Map-case 1.J, Folder 14)
    - "Psychiatric Clinic, Court of General Sessions", by David Wojnarowicz and Kiki Smtih, undated (Map-case 1.J, Folder 15)
    - "Romulus and Remus Silkscreen Pt. 1", undated (Map-case 1.J, Folder 16)
    - "Snowflakes - White, Snowman - Dark" Double Lithograph, undated (Map-case 1.J, Folder 17)
    - Stencils, undated (Map-case 1.J, Folder 18)
    - Various supermarket posters, undated (Map-case 1.J, Folder 19)
    - Various supermarket posters (some altered), undated (Map-case 1.J, Folder 20)
  - Subseries D: Source/Background Material
    - Source: Bullseye targets; anatomical charts of fish and chicken, undated (Map-case 1.J, Folder 21)
    - Source: Two Circus posters w/ tigers; poster, "Anatomical Chart of the Acupressure Points" (altered); poster: tribesmen shooting arrows; fragment of evil clowns poster, undated (Map-case 1.J, Folder 22)
  - Subseries E: Plans
    - "Vaccinate Your God", undated (Map-case 1.J, Folder 23)
  - Subseries G: Other People's Art
    - Kiki Smith, "Cause I'm on My Own Time," 4/28/84, 1984 (Map-case 1.J, Folder 24)
- Accretions 2001 - Media
  - VHS: David Wojnarowicz text voice-over, Fear of Disclosure material [Royal S. Marks AIDS Activist Video Collection], undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - VHS: Fear of Disclosure dancer source material [Royal S. Marks AIDS Activist Video Collection], undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - VHS: David Wojnarowicz speech at memorial service for Phil Zwickler 6/1/91 [Estate Project/NYPL], 1991 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - VHS: Fear of Disclosure source materials - David Wojnarowicz images 11/1989 [Royal S. Marks AIDS Activist Video Collection] (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - VHS: Fear of Disclosure, David Wojnarowicz and Phil Zwickler 1989 [Royal S. Marks AIDS Activist Video Collection] (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - VHS: Fear of Disclosure, Phil Zwickler and David Wojnarowicz text [Royal S. Marks AIDS Activist Video Collection], undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - VHS: Fear of Disclosure text - source material 8/1989 [Royal S. Marks AIDS Activist Video Collection] (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Audiocassette Sony 90: Interview w/ David Wojnarowicz by Adam Kuby 9/14/91 [Gift of Adam Kuby 6/29/01], 1991 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - DAT: JAG #258-Where Evil Dwells., undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Accretions 2001 - Series VI: Biographical
  - Subseries E: Taxes, Receipts, and Legal Documents
    - Correspondence re: Wojnarowicz Published Works and Visual Arts, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Estate Appraisal by P. P. O. W., undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Freedman and Fish Correspondence re: Will and Last Testament, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Will and Last Testament, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Legal Documents, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Legal Documents, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Taxes, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - 16 mm Reel-JAG #240 and #255-Where Evil Dwells., undated (Box 3, Folder no number)
- Subseries F: Commercial Audiotapes
  - Subseries E: Commercial Audiotapes, undated (Box 20, Folder no number)
  - Subseries E: Commercial Audiotapes, undated (Box 21, Folder no number)
  - Subseries E: Commercial Audiotapes, undated (Box 22, Folder no number)
  - Subseries E: Commercial Audiotapes, undated (Box 23, Folder no number)
  - Subseries E: Commercial Audiotapes, undated (Box 24, Folder no number)
  - Subseries E: Commercial Audiotapes, undated (Box 25, Folder no number)
  - Subseries E: Commercial Audiotapes, undated (Box 26, Folder no number)